<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data descriptions on COVID-19 mobility</title>
    <link>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data descriptions on COVID-19 mobility</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Movement Maps</title>
      <link>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/movement_maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/movement_maps/</guid>
      <description>Movement Maps For understanding How people move we use so-called &amp;ldquo;Movement Maps&amp;rdquo;, which are provided by the Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Data for Good initiative. Specifically, we use a combination of Movement maps at tile level and administrative region level (see Granularity and Further preprocessing).
Description: A Movement map seperates the country into different areas. It then reports the number of users that travel between areas, for three eight hour time windows each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Population Density Maps</title>
      <link>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/population_density_maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/population_density_maps/</guid>
      <description>Population Density Maps For understanding Where people are we use &amp;ldquo;Population Density Maps&amp;rdquo;, which are provided by the Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Data for Good initiative. Specifically, we use Population density maps at the tile level (see Granularity).
Description: A Population density map seperates the country into different areas, and for each it counts the number of users that spend most of their time there, for three eight hour time windows each day. For example, for the 08–16 (working hours) time window on May 4, there may be 52.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telco data description</title>
      <link>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/telco_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covid19.compute.dtu.dk/data-description/telco_data/</guid>
      <description>Movement maps using telco data These data show the number of daily trips between Danish Municipalities, estimated from aggregated mobile phone data provided by four large telecommunication companies. It is not possible to infer individual mobility from this dataset. Data covers the period from 1. February of 2020.
Origin of data The data set was delivered by four major Danish telcos to Statistics Denmark (DST) to help the Danish State Serum Institute (SSI) - the Danish equivalent to the US&amp;rsquo;s CDC - to model the spread of COVID-19 and understand population behavior in response to various lock-down/mitigation measures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>